Guide to the Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings 1940-1952
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Milner Discs, 1940-1952
  - 1941 June 15-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 46)
    - (Aircheck – Accidental) Democratic Wallace for Maw Political, 1944 October 25 (Track 163)
    - Paganini Quartet 5, Paganini Quartet 2, 1948 June 11 (Track 164)
    - Campaign Results Roosevelt – Dewey 1944 Election 21 and 23, Undated (Track 165)
  - 1941 June-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 46)
    - KSL - 660B Lord Hallifax cut from CBS Part IV, KSL - 661A Lord Hallifax Address cut from CBS Part II, 1941 March 25; 1941 March 24 (Track 162)
    - (Aircheck – Accidental) Democratic Wallace for Maw Political, 1944 October 25 (Track 163)
    - Paganini Quartet 5, Paganini Quartet 2, 1948 June 11 (Track 164)
    - Campaign Results Roosevelt – Dewey 1944 Election 21 and 23, Undated (Track 165)
  - 1944 October-1949 February, Compact disc (Disc 47)
    - Campaign Results Roosevelt – Dewey 1944 Election 21 and 23, Undated (Track 165)
    - "Mind in the Shadow" Recorded from C.B.S. Part 1, Unknown Drama, 1949 February 2, undated (Track 166)
    - Gov. J.W. Brickes Political Aircheck Pt. 1 7066 (10-21-44), 1944 October 21 (Track 167)
    - Paganini Quartet 1, Paganini Quartet 5, 1948 June 14 (Track 168)
  - 1944 October-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 48)
    - Paganini Quartet 1, Paganini Quartet 5, 1948 June 14 (Track 168)
    - Paganini 6, 4 Missed Start, 1948 June 10 (Track 169)
    - Salt Lake Tribune Political Forum, 1944 October 12; 1944 October 19 (Track 170)
    - WBS – Disk 127 The Miracle at Christmas starring Michael Mitchell A/F Part 1, WBS – Disk 127 The Miracle at Christmas starring Michael Mitchell A/F Part 2, Undated (Track 171)
  - 1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 49)
    - WBS – Disk 127 The Miracle at Christmas starring Michael Mitchell A/F Part 1, WBS – Disk 127 The Miracle at Christmas starring Michael Mitchell A/F Part 2, Undated (Track 171)
    - Cut 2 (Jumpy at the End), Cut 4, Undated (Track 172)
    - 2 and 4, 8 and 10 (Not Finished Due To Skipping), 1948 June 9 (Track 173)
    - 6A Piano Duo Concert – Ann. Rex Campbell, 5A News of the World, Alan Jensen, Undated (Track 174)
  - Undated, Compact disc (Disc 50)
    - 6A Piano Duo Concert – Ann. Rex Campbell, 5A News of the World, Alan Jensen, Undated (Track 174)
    - 2A To Each His Own, Jack Barrel Orchestra, 3A News Music, Undated (Track 175)
    - Nab-Lang-Worth – No. 308 The Lang-Worth Gauchos, South American Novelty Orchestra, Nab-Lang-Worth – No. 307 The Lang-Worth Foursome, Undated (Track 176)
  - 1948 January-1948 March, Compact disc (Disc 51)
    - Utah Symphony Orchestra Recorded from KSL Part 2, Utah Symphony Orchestra, 1948 March 4 (Track 177)
    - Utah Symphony Orchestra Recorded from KSL Part 2, Utah Symphony Orchestra Recorded from KSL Part 4, 1948 January 22 (Track 178)
    - Utah State Symphony Orchestra Part 1, Utah State Symphony Orchestra Part 3, 1948 February 14 (Track 179)
  - 1948 February-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 52)
    - Utah State Symphony Orchestra Part 1, Utah State Symphony Orchestra Part 3, 1948 February 14 (Track 179)
    - Utah State Symphony Orchestra, Utah State Symphony Orchestra Part 2, 1948 February 14 (Track 180)
    - 550A 1 O Sing Ye Unto the Lord (2:50) 3 Have Mercy (4:05), 550B 5 Mass (Part 1) (3:05) 7 Noel (4:16), 1948 June 8 (Track 181)
    - 555A 7 Played by R.L., 555B 9 and 11 Played by R.L., 1948 June 10 (Track 182)
  - 1944 October-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 53)
    - 555A 7 Played by R.L., 555B 9 and 11 Played by R.L., 1948 June 10 (Track 182)
    - Political J. Bracken Yee, 1944 October 28 (Track 183)
    - Nab-Lang-Worth – No. 305 The Lang-Worth Foursome, Nab-Lang-Worth – No. 306 The Lang-Worth Gauchos, South American Novelty Orchestra, Undated (Track 184)
    - Nab-Lang-Worth – No. 312 Lang-Worth Concert Orchestra with Anne Fiora, Soprano, Nab-Lang-Worth – No. 311 The Lang-Worth Gauchos, South American Novelty Orchestra, Undated (Track 185)
  - 1944 October, Compact disc (Disc 54)
    - 2 Buck in the Bucket Sing-A-Long Club, 20B, Undated (Track 186)
    - 18, 20A, Undated (Track 187)
    - Political Adam S. Bennion, 1944 October 26 (Track 188)
  - 1941-1948 July, Compact disc (Disc 55)
    - 918B Gen. Conf., 1941 (Track 189)
    - KSL – Salute to the Tabernacle Choir on 20th Anniversary by Frank Stanton CBS President. Introduction by Ivor Sharp, KSL – Church of the Air Part 1 (Skips too much), 1948 July 15; 1948 April 4 (Track 190)
    - Parmer From Washington Presenting An American Statesman Looks at the World's Christmas Scene" U.S. Senator Elbert D. Thomas (Democrat-UT), Undated (Track 191)
    - Parmer From Washington Interview with Senator Thomas From Utah, 1947 July 17 (Track 192)
  - 1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 56)
    - Paganini Quartet 1. (7:35), Paganini Quartet 7 (16:20), 1948 June 11 (Track 193)
    - Sherris Musical Novelettes – Johnny Gart: Organist and Accordionist, Jack Shilkret: Pianist 1A and 1B, Undated (Track 194)
    - Unknown News (Part of it skipped), Unknown News 2 (Beginning Skipped), Undated (Track 195)
  - 1944 October-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 57)
    - Unknown News (Part of it skipped), Unknown News 2 (Beginning Skipped), Undated (Track 195)
    - Political Adam Bennion from Hotel Utah, 1944 November 6 (Track 196)
    - Political Adam S. Bennion, 1944 November 4 (Track 197)
    - Tribune Telegram Political Forum 7120, 1944 October 26 (Track 198)
    - W. Malone, 1946 August 18 (Track 199)
  - 1944 October-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 58)
    - Political Barton Masser 7178, 1944 November 4 (Track 200)
    - 10 Piano Duo, 1 Air Force Day, Undated (Track 201)
    - 22 and 24, Undated (Track 202)
    - J. Bracken Lee Gov. Comm. Spot Ann. 1-9 Inclusive, Omit 6, 1944 November 3 (Track 203)
  - 1944 October-1946 August, Compact disc (Disc 59)
    - 1944 Election Results 27 and 25, Undated (Track 204)
    - 34 1944 Election Results, Dewey – Roosevelt, Undated (Track 205)
    - Paganini Quartet 2, Paganini Quartet 5, 1948 June 10 (Track 206)
  - 1940 October-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 60)
    - Bishop Wirthlen Part 1 Bishop Meeting, 1940 October (Track 207)
    - J. Bracken Lee Original 14 Min 45 Sec, 1944 November 5 (Track 208)
    - Paganini Quartet 2, Paganini Quartet 6 + 8, 1948 June 14 (Track 209)
  - 1944 November-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 61)
    - 3 and 5 Played on KSL (Bad Recording, skips), 1948 June 16 (Track 210)
    - 4 and 2 Played on KSL by R.L., 1948 June 16 (Track 211)
    - Dr. Francis Kirkham Dubbing, 1944 November 5 (Track 212)
    - Part 1 David O. M'Kay Bishops Meeting – Praise, Rix College Chorus "God So Loved the World", Undated (Track 213)
  - 1940 August-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 62)
    - Part 1 David O. M'Kay Bishops Meeting – Praise, Rix College Chorus "God So Loved the World", Undated (Track 213)
    - 551B 9 Holy Radiant Night (4:58) 11 Praise To The Lord Almighty (4:05), 551A 2 Adoramus TE (2:50) 4 Spirit Also Helpeth Us (5:48), 1948 June 8 (Track 214)
    - Political – Tribune Round Table, Senator Thomas + Two Others, 1944 November 1 (Track 215)
    - General Geo. C. Marshall Speaks to National (?), Don Colton Pgm, 1940 September 16; 1940 August 31 (Track 216)
  - 1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 63)
    - Cut 1 and Cut 6, Undated (Track 217)
    - Cut 5 Part 2, Cut 7 (Encore) Andantino Op 74 Hayden, Undated (Track 218)
    - Cut 3 (Recording Not Finished), Cut 5 Part 1 Paganini Quartet, Undated (Track 219)
    - Cut 1 (Skips Throughout), 7 (Skips Throughout), 1948 June 18 (Track 220)
  - 1944 September-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 64)
    - 533A 1,3, 533B 5-6, 1948 June 10; 1948 June 9 (Track 221)
    - 1944 Election Results, Roosevelt – Dewey 33, Undated (Track 222)
    - KSL - 4869 Utah State Symphony Part II, KSL - 4371 Utah State Symphony Part IV, 1947 March 5 (Track 223)
    - Political Tribune Telegram 6855, 1944 September 15; 1944 September 21 (Track 224)
  - 1944 September, Compact disc (Disc 65)
    - Political Tribune Telegram 6855, 1944 September 15; 1944 September 21 (Track 224)
    - 1944 Elections, Roosevelt – Dewey 32 and 30, Undated (Track 225)
    - 3R Corn Cobblers Minuet (Part of Label Missing), 8 Music, Undated (Track 226)
  - Undated, Compact disc (Disc 66)
    - Election Results, Roosevelt – Dewey 1944, 16B and 14, Undated (Track 227)
    - 1944 Election Results, Roosevelt – Dewey 28 and 26, Undated (Track 228)
    - 29 and 31, Undated (Track 229)
  - 1951 March, Compact disc (Disc 67)
    - 29 and 31, Undated (Track 229)
    - Nab-Lang Worth 741 "Symphonic Swing" by Szath-Myri, Nab-Lang-Worth 742 Lang-Worth Military Band, Undated (Track 230)
    - Program No. 501 The Modern Melody Trio with Lew White, Andy Sannella, and Harry Breuer, Program No. 502 The Modern Melody Trio with Lew White, And Sannella, and Harry Breuer, Undated (Track 231)
    - 6391 Children's Friend "Looking Doll", 1951 March 17 (Track 232)
  - 1950 May-1950 August, Compact disc (Disc 68)
    - Children's Friend "Jug Wit", Children's Friend of the Air "Scowly Owl", 1950 August 12; 1950 August 19 (Track 234)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – East + West, 1950 May 20 (Track 235)
  - 1950 January-1950 July, Compact disc (Disc 69)
    - Children's Friend – The Lost Puppy, Children's Friend of the Air – The Liberty Bell, 1950 July 15; 1950 July 1 (Track 236)
    - Children's Friend of the Air - The Lucky Carl, Children's Friend of the Air – The Beavers Build A New Dam, 1950 June 24; 1950 January 3 (Track 237)
  - 1950 April-1950 July, Compact disc (Disc 70)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Chico", 5965B Hawkens, 1950 July 29; 1950 July 28 (Track 238)
    - Children's Friend – Hoppity Henry Hare, Children's Friend of the Air "Stormy River", 1950 April 1; 1950 April 22 (Track 239)
  - 1947 July-1950 April, Compact disc (Disc 71)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Tiny's Adventure, Miles, 1950 April 29; 1950 April 28 (Track 240)
    - Children's Friend "The Counting Board, Road of Life, 1947 August 23; 1947 July 25 (Track 241)
  - 1948 October-1950 June, Compact disc (Disc 72)
    - Children's Friend – Birthday Party, The Last Wing, 3866A Miles Salute, 1950 June 10; 1948 October 26 (Track 242)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Gray Donkey of San Rafael, 5125A Miles, 1950 March 18; 1950 March 17 (Track 243)
  - 1950 April-1950 June, Compact disc (Disc 73)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Camera Trap, Children's Friend of the Air – Polly's Easter Sermon, 1950 April 15; 1950 April 8 (Track 244)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Old Nuisance, 1950 May 27 (Track 245)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Stephen + Allen Take Over, 1950 June 17 (Track 246)
  - 1947 April-1950 February, Compact disc (Disc 74)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – So Says Ching Chong, 4758A Air Check W.T. Grant, 1950 January 14; 1949 October 6 (Track 247)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Tobys Triumph" Jerry Burns, 1950 February 25 (Track 248)
    - 16246 "Come Come Ye Saints" Organ – Ed Stoker, Heart Throngs Show, 1947 April 10 (Track 249)
  - 1946 April-1948 January, Compact disc (Disc 75)
    - 16287 Stevenson's – Stoker 14:35 (Very bad recording, skips) 16262 Moods, 1947 April 14 (Track 250)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Her Dream, Windell, 1946 April 28 (Track 251)
    - Dick Tracy, 1948 January 27 (Track 252)
  - 1946 May-1950 October, Compact disc (Disc 76)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Ship That Didn't Turn Back" "Columbus Story", Candy Matsor II, 1950 October 7; 1950 September 11 (Track 253)
    - Heart Throbs of the West "The Old State House", Betty Lane, 1946 May 20; 1946 May 27, 28 (Track 254)
    - 4035B Children's Friend – Magic of New Years Day, Highlights from the World of Sports, 1949 January 1, undated (Track 255)
  - 1946 June-1949 January, Compact disc (Disc 77)
    - 4035B Children's Friend – Magic of New Years Day, Highlights from the World of Sports, 1949 January 1, undated (Track 255)
    - 16121 School Mam Marten – Heart Throbs of the West, From Women of Deseret 14 min. 30 sec., Pilgrim's Hour, 1947 February 28; 1947 February 16 (Track 256)
    - The Children's Friend – The Poison Fruit (Bad Recording), The Woman, 1946 June 22, undated (Track 257)
  - 1946 June-1950 June, Compact disc (Disc 78)
    - The Children's Friend – The Poison Fruit (Bad Recording), The Woman, 1946 June 22, undated (Track 257)
    - 3001B Children's Friend of the Air – The Old Scott Place Mystery (Very Grainy Sound), 3001A Believe It Or Not, 1948 January 31; 1948 January 30 (Track 258)
    - 4743 Schubach Beneke Show Spots Master, Children's Friend of the Air – Birthday Party, Undated; 1950 June 10 (Track 259)
  - 1947 January-1949 December, Compact disc (Disc 79)
    - 4831B Children's Friend – Boat Without A Sail, Henry Morgan 2, 1949 November 12, undated (Track 260)
    - *1670B Children's Friend – Mail Must Go ("Pony Express Centennial Pioneer Story") (Can't Record), 1670A NBC Newsroom ECP, 1947 January 18; 1947 January 17 (Track 261)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Little Tommy Tug Boat", Children's Friend of the Air – The First Xmas, 1949 December 10; 1949 February 24 (Track 262)
  - 1947 March-1949 December, Compact disc (Disc 80)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Little Tommy Tug Boat", Children's Friend of the Air – The First Xmas, 1949 December 10; 1949 February 24 (Track 262)
    - 2905A Children's Friend "Redskin Ransom", 2905B Children's Friend "The Windmill", 1947 March 1; 1948 July 31 (Track 263)
    - Children's Friend – Four Legged Circus Ticket, Children's Friend of the Air – Gift of Time, 1949 August 20; 1949 August 27 (Track 264)
  - 1948 January-1949 November, Compact disc (Disc 81)
    - Children's Friend – Four Legged Circus Ticket, Children's Friend of the Air – Gift of Time, 1949 August 20; 1949 August 27 (Track 264)
    - Children's Friend "Little Daffy Down Delly", Henry Morgan 2, 1949 November 26 (Track 265)
    - Inside – Senator Wilkins – Report From Congress, Children's Friend of the Air – Old Blindeye the Good Ox, 1948 January 24; 1948 July 17 (Track 266)
  - 1948 January-1949 July, Compact disc (Disc 82)
    - Inside – Senator Wilkins – Report From Congress, Children's Friend of the Air – Old Blindeye the Good Ox, 1948 January 24; 1948 July 17 (Track 266)
    - 4459A Children's Friend of the Air – Amnen + Theme live on end (July 9, 1949), 1949 July 9 (Track 267)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "A Treasure of the Heart", Children's Friend – Easter Bunny With the Peachy Pink Tail, 1949 April 23; 1949 April 16 (Track 268)
  - 1946 August-1950 December, Compact disc (Disc 83)
    - 2972B Children's Friend – Mystery in the Green Forest, Bob Ripley's Believe It Or Not, 1948 January 24, undated (Track 269)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Best Thanks Giving Dinner, Children's Friend – Poster Contest, Undated; 1950 December 2 (Track 270)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Carolyn Joyce (8/18/46), 1946 August 18 (Track 271)
  - 1947 December-1948 September, Compact disc (Disc 84)
    - KDYL – Children's Friend of the Air "Petra + the King's Garden", Miles, 1948 September 25; 1948 September 24 (Track 272)
    - Can U Top This Part 1, Children's Friend – Cat That Changed Things, Square Town, Undated; 1947 December 19 (Track 273)
  - 1948 October-1949 April, Compact disc (Disc 85)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Fish That Couldn't Swim", Unesco, 1948 October 2; 1948 October 9 (Track 274)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Doll in the May Basket, Children's Friend Thankful Hearts, Thanksgiving, 1949 April 30; 1948 November 27 (Track 275)
  - 1948 March-1948 October, Compact disc (Disc 86)
    - 3228A Believe it or Not, Children's Friend – Miss Lily Bulb Easter Program, 1948 March 26; 1948 March 27 (Track 276)
    - 3364A Miles, Children's Friend of the Air – Desert Rainbow, 1948 April 8; 1948 April 10 (Track 277)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Jam's Chocolate Cake, Children's Friend of the Air – Ong Loo's Chance, 1948 October 23; 1948 October 16 (Track 278)
  - 1945 February-1948 October, Compact disc (Disc 87)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Jam's Chocolate Cake, Children's Friend of the Air – Ong Loo's Chance (Skips at end), 1948 October 23; 1948 October 16 (Track 278)
    - Zephyr Vinyl (No Name), Undated (Track 279)
    - For Simon Show – Don't Touch 2, Air Check Part 1 + 2 (Can't Record), 1945 February 22, undated (Track 280)
    - Children's Friend "No-Account Job" (Skips), 3753A Children's Friend of the Air "Perotti's Pups", 1948 October 9; 1948 September 18 (Track 281)
  - 1948 October-1949 April, Compact disc (Disc 88)
    - Children's Friend, Ineligible (Skips Very Bad), 1947 November 13, undated (Track 282)
    - Children's Friend – Jack Frost + Squirrel, Radio City, 1948 November 20, undated (Track 283)
  - 1948 October-1949 April, Compact disc (Disc 89)
    - The Magic of Song, 3873A Children's Friend – Halloween, 1948 November 6; 1948 October 30 (Track 284)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Pioneer Mothers, 1946 May 12 (Track 285)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – A Courtship (Skips Bad), July 14 (Track 286)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Old Glory, June 30 (Track 287)
  - 1946 June-1947 July, Compact disc (Disc 90)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Country Doctor, 1946 June 9 (Track 288)
    - Children's Friend "Blinka + the Silver Spoon", Children's Friend of the Air "When Spring Comes to the Rockies" (Skips Bad), Undated (Track 289)
    - 2721A Paint With Pride – Safety Hit Run Driver (Vinyl Broken), March 4 (Track 290)
    - 2181A Sec. Krug Interview – Will Wright M.C., 2181B Children's Friend "Valley of the Moon", 1947 July 31, undated (Track 291)
  - 1947 November-1949 June, Compact disc (Disc 91)
    - Children's Friend – Bracelet That Was Different, Diamonds Square in Salt Lake City – Sparkback Jewel Room, 1947 November 1, undated (Track 292)
    - 4422A Children's Friend – Pepper What A Horse Part I, Children's Friend of the Air "The Giggling Scarecrow", 1949 June 11; 1949 June 25 (Track 293)
  - 1947 May-1951 February, Compact disc (Disc 92)
    - 605004 "Not 'House' William, But 'Our Home'", Unknown Radio Show (Bad Recording), Undated (Track 294)
    - 16174 Heart Throbs of the West – Larken Walters Old Freighters, Undated (Track 295)
    - 16510 "Crossroads Chapel", 16565 Indian Mood (Can't Record), 1947 May 29, undated (Track 296)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Pennies Find A Way, 6349A Miles, 1951 February 10; 1951 February 9 (Track 297)
  - 1950 January-1951 February, Compact disc (Disc 93)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Pennies Find A Way, 6349A Miles, 1951 February 10; 1951 February 9 (Track 297)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Little Sprawly", 5961A Children's Friend of the Air "Wooly Mascots", 1950 September 23 (Track 298)
    - 4985 Children's Friend of the Air – The Pennies Find A Way, 4985 Mendy Carson, 1950 February 4; 1950 January 25 (Track 299)
  - 1940 July-1950 February, Compact disc (Disc 94)
    - 4985 Children's Friend of the Air – The Pennies Find A Way, 4985 Mendy Carson, 1950 February 4; 1950 January 25 (Track 299)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Pioneer Jonas", Unknown, 1940 July 22, undated (Track 300)
    - 1678 Bing Crosby Show "Mr. Radio" (Bad Quality and Skips), Sidney Does Fishing Opening (Can't Record), 1947 January 25, undated (Track 301)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Little Liza Honey Bee (Bad Quality Skips), 1460A Child…(?) Part 1, Undated (Track 302)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Lame Toby (Bad Recording, End Cut Off Due To Skipping), Console Magician – Take this to Mr. Carmen, 1946 March 24 (Track 303)
  - 1946 March-1949 August, Compact disc (Disc 95)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Lame Toby (Bad Recording, End Cut Off Due To Skipping), Console Magician – Take this to Mr. Carmen, 1946 March 24 (Track 303)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Story of Martha Ann Fox Taylor, Unknown, 1948 July 28, undated (Track 304)
    - Children's Friend – Uncle Nathan's Fancy Vest, News of the World - Hiroshima, 1949 August 6, undated (Track 305)
    - 50140 "Easy Listenin'" Wasatch Cleaners, Dyers and Furriers – Ken Linn, 50140 Heart Throbs of the West John Cotton Wood Carver (Not finished, Skipping), 1947 April 4; 1947 March 28 (Track 306)
  - 1946 May-1948 May, Compact disc (Disc 96)
    - 50140 "Easy Listenin'" Wasatch Cleaners, Dyers and Furriers – Ken Linn, 50140 Heart Throbs of the West John Cotton Wood Carver (Not finished, Skipping), 1947 April 4; 1947 March 28 (Track 306)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Strange White House, 1946 May 19 (Track 307)
    - Heart Throbs of the West "Pioneer Homes" (Skips), Coin Themes (?) (Can't Record), 1946 May 5, undated (Track 308)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Chief Kanosh the Peacemaker (Skips), Traffic Safety (Skips Bad), 1946 July 14, undated (Track 309)
    - Children's Friend – The Blue Vase, Children's Friend of the Air "2t is Written", 1948 May 1; 1948 May 8 (Track 310)
  - 1947 October-1951 February, Compact disc (Disc 97)
    - Children's Friend – The Blue Vase, Children's Friend of the Air "2t is Written", 1948 May 1; 1948 May 8 (Track 310)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Burro and the Beans", 6333A Children's Friend "Greedy Little Turtle", 1951 February 3; 1951 January 28 (Track 311)
    - Children's Friend – Kent's Halloween Prank, 2375 Children's Friend – Happy Hearts, 1947 October 18; 1947 October 11 (Track 312)
  - 1947 October-1951 May, Compact disc (Disc 98)
    - Children's Friend – Kent's Halloween Prank, 2375 Children's Friend – Happy Hearts, 1947 October 18; 1947 October 11 (Track 312)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Wee Willie and the Halloween Surprise, Children's Friend of the Air – Conspiracy in Black and White, 1950 October 28; 1950 November 4 (Track 313)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Manuel and the Old Old Lady", Children's Friend of the Air "The Wizard of YeeyooValley", 1951 May 5; 1951 April 21 (Track 314)
  - 1951 February-1951 May, Compact disc (Disc 99)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Manuel and the Old Old Lady", Children's Friend of the Air "The Wizard of YeeyooValley", 1951 May 5; 1951 April 21 (Track 314)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Nate and Abraham Lincoln, Children's Friend of the Air – Special Delivery, 1951 February 17 (Track 315)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Goat That Wouldn't Neigh", Children's Friend of the Air "Peter Pelican Repays A Debt", 1951 March 3; 1951 March 10 (Track 316)
  - 1945 February-1951 March, Compact disc (Disc 100)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Goat That Wouldn't Neigh", Children's Friend of the Air "Peter Pelican Repays A Debt", 1951 March 3; 1951 March 10 (Track 316)
    - 5000A, 5000B Valley Fun Finders 1 (Can't Record), Undated (Track 317)
    - 4 Presto, When Siren Sounds 3 (Can't Record), 1945 March 8; 1945 March 1 (Track 318)
    - When Siren Sounds PGM 1 Utah Accident and Health Club, When Siren Sounds PGM 2 Utah Accident and Health Club, 1945 February 15; 1945 February 22 (Track 319)
  - 1945 February-1951 March, Compact disc (Disc 101)
    - When Siren Sounds PGM 1 Utah Accident and Health Club, When Siren Sounds PGM 2 Utah Accident and Health Club, 1945 February 15; 1945 February 22 (Track 319)
    - "Wild Irish Rose" 2- When Irish Eyes Are Smiley, 5364 Miles (No Finished), Undated; 1951 February 23 (Track 320)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Rugged Men of the West, Adam Sharps Goes West, 1946 May 31 (Track 321)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Just A Squall", Children's Friend of the Air - Good Fer Nuttin Dog, 1949 October 1; 1949 October 8 (Track 322)
  - 1947 Septemer-1949 October, Compact disc (Disc 102)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Just A Squall", Children's Friend of the Air - Good Fer Nuttin Dog, 1949 October 1; 1949 October 8 (Track 322)